Guide to the Burney Family Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Burney Family Collection, Series I
  - JAMARD, PRIOR OF ROCWUEFORT
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1797, 1803 (Box 11, Folder 812)
  - JAMES, JOHN, CA. 1782-1865
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1860 Sep-Nov (Box 11, Folder 813)
  - JOHNSON, REGINALD BRIMLEY, 1867-1932
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1892 Oct 25 (Box 11, Folder 814)
  - JOHUN, F.
    - Letters to Frances Anne Burney, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 815)
  - JONES, HUGH CHAMBERS, 1783-1862
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1848 Jan 9 (Box 11, Folder 816)
  - JONES & FORESTER, SOLICITORS
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1889 Jan 26 (Box 11, Folder 817)
  - JORTIN, LOUISA (MATY)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1788 Mar 14 (Box 11, Folder 818)
  - KAYE, JOHN, BISHOP OF LINCOLN, 1783-1853
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1805 Sep 30 (Box 11, Folder 819)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1801-04 (Box 11, Folder 820)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1805 (Box 11, Folder 821)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806-07 (Box 11, Folder 822)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 Mar-May (Box 11, Folder 823)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 Jun-Dec (Box 11, Folder 824)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1809 (Box 11, Folder 825)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810-15 (Box 11, Folder 826)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1816 Oct 15 (Box 11, Folder 827)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1816 Jun 24 (Box 11, Folder 828)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1817-19 (Box 11, Folder 829)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1820 Nov-[ca. 1820-27] (Box 11, Folder 830)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1821 Feb-Sep (Box 11, Folder 831)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1823-24 (Box 11, Folder 832)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1826 (Box 11, Folder 833)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1827 (Box 11, Folder 834)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1828-30 (Box 11, Folder 835)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1831-32 (Box 11, Folder 836)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1833-43 (Box 11, Folder 837)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1846-52 (Box 11, Folder 838)
  - KAYE, WILLIAM FREDERICK JOHN
    [Archdeacon of Lincoln, 1823-1913]
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1853] Feb 24 (Box 11, Folder 839)
  - KEATE, WILLIAM, 1739-95
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1794 (Box 11, Folder 840)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1795 (Box 11, Folder 841)
  - KEATS, SIR RICHARD GOODWIN, 1757-1834
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1832 May-Nov (Box 11, Folder 842)
  - KELLY, HUGH, 1739-1777
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 843)
  - KEMBLE, JOHN PHILIP, 1757-1823
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1793-1817 (Box 12, Folder 844)
  - KEMBLE, PRISCILLA (HOPKINS) BRERETON
    [1756-1843]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [ca. 1800]-1810 (Box 12, Folder 845)
  - KER, M. W.
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1897 Mar 26 (Box 12, Folder 846)
  - KETT, HENRY
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1790]-92 (Box 12, Folder 847)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804-13 (Box 12, Folder 848)
  - KIDD, THOMAS, 1770-1850
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1798-1809 (Box 12, Folder 849)
  - KING, EDWARD, BISHOP OF LINCOLN
    [1829-1910]
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1891 Nov 18 (Box 12, Folder 850)
  - KING, THOMAS, 1730-1805
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802 May 22 (Box 12, Folder 851)
  - KING, WALKER, BISHOP OF ROCHESTER
    [1752-1827]
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1813-[ca. 1815] (Box 12, Folder 852)
  - KINNAIRD, DOUGLAS JAMES WILLIAM
    [1788-1830]
    - Letter to [Charles Burney, D.D.], 1814 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 853)
  - KITCHIN, GEORGE WILLIAM, 1827-1912
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1888 Jan 8 (Box 12, Folder 854)
  - KLAPROTKY, H.
    - Letter to [Charles Parr Burney], 1834 May 26 (Box 12, Folder 855)
  - KNIGHT, MISS [ELLIS CORNELIA]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus. D., 1801 Aug 7 (Box 12, Folder 856)
  - KNIGHT, RICHARD PAYNE, 1750-1824
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1782-1805 (Box 12, Folder 857)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 (Box 12, Folder 858)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1811, 1813 (Box 12, Folder 859)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 (Box 12, Folder 860)
  - KNOLLYS, AMICIA MARY
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 861)
  - LAFAYETTE, MARIE JOSEPH PAUL YVES ROCH
    [Gilbert du Motier, marquis de, 1757-1834]
    - Letter to Alexandre d'Arblay, [ca. 1810] (Box 12, Folder 862)
  - LAGRENCE, V.
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1837 Aug 12 (Box 12, Folder 863)
  - LANGTON, BENNET, 1737-1801
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1788]-[ca. 1799] (Box 12, Folder 864)
  - LANSDOWNE, HENRY PETTY FITZMAURICE, 1780-1863
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806-15 (Box 12, Folder 865)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1824 Jul 14 (Box 12, Folder 866)
  - LATROBE, CHRISTIAN IGNATIUS, 1758-1836
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1791-1803 (Box 12, Folder 867)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1824 Mar-Aug (Box 12, Folder 868)
    - Letter to Mrs. (Charlotte Ann Francis) Broome, 1808 Mar 31 (Box 12, Folder 869)
  - LAW, GEOGRE HENRY, 1761-1845
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1815 May 22 (Box 12, Folder 870)
  - LAW, JAMES THOMAS, 1790-1876
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1823, 1824 (Box 12, Folder 871)
  - LAW, JOHN, BISHOP OF ELPHIN, 1745-1810
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1816 Jul 11 (Box 12, Folder 872)
  - LAWRENCE, SIR THOMAS, 1769-1830
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [ca. 1790]-1811 (Box 12, Folder 873)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1826, 1828 (Box 12, Folder 874)
    - Letter to Rosette Burney, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 875)
  - LE BAS, CHARLES WILLIAM, 1779-1861
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1813 Jul-Aug (Box 12, Folder 876)
  - LEEDS, CATHERINE (ANGUISH) OSBORNE
    [Duchess of, 1764-1837]
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, [1788] (Box 12, Folder 877)
  - LEGGE, EDWARD A., BISHOP OF OXFORD
    [1767-1827]
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1816-17 (Box 12, Folder 878)
  - LEITCH, WILLIAM LEIGHTON, 1804-1883
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1861 Nov 26 (Box 12, Folder 879)
  - LEMPRIERE, JOHN, [1760]-1824
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1788 Nov 5 (Box 12, Folder 880)
  - LEVIEN, F.
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1897 Apr 13 (Box 12, Folder 881)
  - LEWIS, FREDERICK CHRISTIAN, 1779-1856
    - Letter to [Charles Parr Burney], n.d. (Box 12, Folder 882)
  - LEWIS, WILLIAM THOMAS, [1748]-1811
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [1790?] (Box 12, Folder 883)
  - LIND, JAMES, 1736-1812
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus. D., 1774 Nov 11 (Box 12, Folder 884)
  - LINDSAY, LADY CHARLOTTE (NORTH)
    [d. 1849]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 885)
  - LINDSAY, JAMES, D. 1821
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1821 Feb 12 (Box 12, Folder 886)
  - LINLEY, WILLIAM, 1771-1835
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, [pre-1835] (Box 12, Folder 887)
  - LIPSCOMBE, CHRISTOPHER, BISHOP OF
    [Jamaica, 1781-1843]
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1816 Jun 24 (Box 12, Folder 888)
  - LOCKE, WILLIAM, 1732-1810
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1785 Dec 6 (Box 12, Folder 889)
  - LOCKER, EDWARD HAWKE, 1777-1849
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1832 Sep 7 (Box 12, Folder 890)
    - Letter to Frances Bentley (Young) Burney, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 891)
  - LONSDALE, JOHN, BISHOP OF LICHFIELD
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1827-41 (Box 12, Folder 892)
  - LONSDALE, WILLIAM LOWTHER, 1ST EARL OF, 1757-1844
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1804-08 (Box 12, Folder 893)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1809-12 (Box 12, Folder 894)
  - LOUTHERBOURG, PHILIP JAMES DE, 1740-1812
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [post 1783] (Box 12, Folder 895)
  - LOWE, EDWARD C., 1823-1912
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1890 (Box 12, Folder 896)
  - LUCAN, MARGARET (SMITH) BINGHAM, COUNTESS OF
    [d. 1814]
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1797], n.d. (Box 12, Folder 897)
  - LUCAS, EDWARD VERRALL, 1868-1938
    - Letter to Charles Burney V, 1904 Feb 29 (Box 12, Folder 898)
  - LUMISDEN, ANDREW, 1720-1801
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1776, 1780 (Box 12, Folder 899)
  - LYALL, WILLIAM ROWE, 1788-1857
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 900)
  - LYNES, JOHN
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1841 Oct 20 (Box 12, Folder 901)
  - LYTTLETON, WILLIAM HENRY LYTTELTON, 3D BARON
    [1782-1837]
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1833 Jun 21 (Box 12, Folder 902)
  - MACAULAY, THOMAS BABINGTON MACAULAY, 1ST BARON
    - Letter to Oliver J. Jones, 1842 Oct 28 (Box 12, Folder 903)
  - MCDERMOTT, WILLIAM
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1832 Dec 12 (Box 12, Folder 904)
  - MACKNIGHT, THOMAS
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [ca. 1788-91?] (Box 12, Folder 905)
  - MACLAGAN, WILLIAM DALRYMPLE, ARCHBISHOP OF YORK
    [1826-1910]
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1886 Jun, Jul (Box 12, Folder 906)
  - MACMILLAN, ALEXANDER, 1818-1896
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1888 Dec 1 (Box 12, Folder 907)
  - MALONE, EDMOND, 1741-1812
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1810 Nov 19 (Box 12, Folder 908)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1811 Aug 15 (Box 12, Folder 909)
  - MALTBY, EDWARD, BISHOP OF DURHAM, 1770-1859
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808, 1815 (Box 12, Folder 910)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, [1840]-[ca. 1850] (Box 12, Folder 911)
  - MANCINI, GIAMBATISTA
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1776 Jun 18 (Box 12, Folder 912)
  - MANNERS-SUTTON, CHARLES, ARCHBISHOP OF CANTERBURY
    [1775-1828]
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806-14 (Box 12, Folder 913)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 Feb 23 (Box 12, Folder 914)
  - MANNING, HENRY EDWARD, CARDINAL, 1808-1892
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1842, 1843 (Box 12, Folder 915)
  - MANSEL, WILLIAM LORT, BISHOP OF BRISTOL, 1753-1920
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808-16 (Box 12, Folder 916)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1819 May 21 (Box 12, Folder 917)
  - MANT, RICHARD, BISHOP OF DOWN, 1776-1848
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1825 Apr, May (Box 12, Folder 918)
  - MANVERS, ANNE ORTON (MILLS) PIERREPONT, COUNTESS
    [1756-1832]
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1806]-11 (Box 12, Folder 919)
  - MARA, GERTRUD ELISABETH SCHMELING, 1749-1833
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1783 Nov 12 (Box 12, Folder 920)
  - MARCHETTI, LUIGI MATTEI
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1781 May 22 (Box 12, Folder 921)
  - MARKLAND, JAMES HEYWOOD, 1788-1864
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1850 Feb 18 (Box 12, Folder 922)
  - MARSH, HERBERT, BISHOP OF PETERBOROUGH, 1757-1839
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1816 Jul 27 (Box 12, Folder 923)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1824 Dec 8 (Box 12, Folder 924)
  - MARTIN, L. S.
    - Letter to [Charles Parr Burney], 1818 Oct 22 (Box 12, Folder 925)
  - MARTINELLI, VINCENZIO, 1702-1785
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1760, 1770 (Box 12, Folder 926)
  - MARTINI, GIAMBATTISTA, 1706-1784
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1771-79 (Box 12, Folder 927)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1780-84 (Box 12, Folder 928)
  - MASKELYNE, NEVIL, 1732-1811
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 929)
  - MASON, WILLIAM, 1724-1797
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1771-95 (Box 13, Folder 930)
  - MATHEWS, J. C.
    - Letter to Charles Burney V, 1907 Nov 23 (Box 13, Folder 931)
  - MATHIAS, THOMAS JAMES, 1754-1835
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1805 Apr 16 (Box 13, Folder 932)
    - Letters to Mrs. Charlotte Broome, 1809-[10] (Box 13, Folder 933)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1810 Oct 13 (Box 13, Folder 934)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1805-14 (Box 13, Folder 935)
    - Letters to Marianne Francis, [ca. 1810-14], 1812 (Box 13, Folder 936)
  - MATY, H.
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [1787?] Mar 11 (Box 13, Folder 937)
  - MATY, PAUL HENRY, 1745-1787
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [ca. 1785] (Box 13, Folder 938)
  - MAURICE, THOMAS, 1754-1824
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [ca. 1804]-[16] (Box 13, Folder 939)
  - MEATH, REGINALD BRABAZON, 12TH EARL OF, 1841-1929
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1889 Apr 6 (Box 13, Folder 940)
  - MELBOURNE, ELIZABETH (MILBANKE) LAMB, VISCOUNTESS
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 941)
  - MILLER, EDWARD, 1731-1806
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1796-99 (Box 13, Folder 942)
  - MILMAN, HENRY HART, DEAN OF ST. PAUL'S, 1791-1868
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1849] Nov 12 (Box 13, Folder 943)
  - MINGOTTI, REGINA, 1728-1807
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus. D., [ca. 1771] (Box 13, Folder 944)
  - MITFORD, JOHN, 1781-1859
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, [post 1840]-46 (Box 13, Folder 945)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1848-[ca. 1852] (Box 13, Folder 946)
  - MONK, JAMES HENRY, BISHOP OF GLOUCESTER, 1784-1856
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810-15 (Box 13, Folder 947)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1824-29 (Box 13, Folder 948)
  - MONNET, JEAN
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1771 Jul 28 (Box 13, Folder 949)
  - MONTAGU, BASIL, 1770-1851
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1812 Jun 21 (Box 13, Folder 950)
  - MONTAGU, ELIZABETH ROBINSON, 1720-1800
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, [1782] (Box 13, Folder 951)
  - MONTGOMERY, HENRY HUTCHINSON, BISHOP OF TASMANIA
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1889 Apr 4 (Box 13, Folder 952)
  - MORELLET, ANDRé, 1727-1818
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [post 1803] Jun 24 (Box 13, Folder 953)
  - MORLEY, JOHN, D. 1842
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790 May 28 (Box 13, Folder 954)
  - MORNINGTON, GARRETT WELLESLEY, 1ST EARL OF
    [1735-1781]
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1773-77 (Box 13, Folder 955)
  - [MORSE], CLARISSA
    - Letter to Sarah (Rose) Burney, [1764] Jun 14 (Box 13, Folder 956)
  - MORTLOCK, [EDMUND DAVY], 1787-1873
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1853] Mar 2 (Box 13, Folder 957)
  - MOSELEY, BENJAMIN, M.D., 1742-1819
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1799 (Box 13, Folder 958)
  - MUMSSEN, DR. J.
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1772 Oct 16 (Box 13, Folder 959)
  - MUNN, PAUL SANDBY, 1773-1845
    - Letter to Mrs. Frances Bentley (Young) Burney, [1825] Mar 31 (Box 13, Folder 960)
  - MURPHY, ARTHUR, 1727-1805
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 961)
  - MURRAY, GEORGE, BISHOP OF ROCHESTER, 1784-1860
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1846-55 (Box 13, Folder 962)
  - MUSGRAVE, GEORGE MUSGRAVE, 1798-1833
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1833 Feb 21 (Box 13, Folder 963)
    - Letter to Frances Bentley (Young) Burney, 1822 May 19 (Box 13, Folder 964)
  - NARES, ROBERT, 1753-1829
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1812 (Box 13, Folder 965)
  - NARES, EDWARD, 1762-1841
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1809-1825 (Box 13, Folder 966)
  - NARES, ROBERT, 1753-1829
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1816?] Jul 7 (Box 13, Folder 967)
  - NICHOLS, JOHN, 1745-1826
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [post 1795] Sep 14 (Box 13, Folder 968)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, [1818]-25 (Box 13, Folder 969)
    - Letter to Mr. and Mrs. Charles Parr Burney, 1826 [Nov 9] (Box 13, Folder 970)
  - NOLLEKENS, JOSEPH, 1737-1823
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1803-15 (Box 13, Folder 971)
  - NORRIS, J. A.
    - Letter to Charles Burney V, 1906 Oct 29 (Box 13, Folder 972)
  - NORTH, BROWNLOW, BISHOP OF WINCHESTER, 1741-1820
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1782-1811, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 973)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1809, 1817 (Box 13, Folder 974)
  - NORTH, HENRIETTA MARIA (BANNISTER), D. 1796
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1785 Aug 28 (Box 13, Folder 975)
  - NORTH, MONTAGU
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1771 May 31 (Box 13, Folder 976)
  - FINDLATER AND SEAFIELD, JAMES OGILVY, 7TH AND 4TH
    [earl of, 1750-1811]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1781 Jan-Mar (Box 13, Folder 977)
  - OGILVIE, WILLIAM, 1736-1819
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1791-1810 (Box 13, Folder 978)
  - O'KEEFE, JOHN, 1747-1833
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 979)
  - ORD, ANN (DILLINGHAM), 1726-1808
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1776?]-1807 (Box 13, Folder 980)
  - ORFORD, GEORGE WALPOLE, 3RD EARL OF, 1730-1791
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1783 Sep 9 (Box 13, Folder 981)
  - OSBORN, JOHN
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1773 Jan 20 (Box 13, Folder 982)
  - OUSELEY, SIR FREDERICK ARTHUR GORE, BART.
    [1825-1889]
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1882 May 17 (Box 13, Folder 983)
  - PACCHIEROTTI, GASPARO, 1744-1821
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1778-87 (Box 13, Folder 984)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1792-1806 (Box 13, Folder 985)
  - PAGET, FRANCIS EDWARD, 1806-1882
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1898 Mar 1 (Box 13, Folder 986)
  - PALMER, EDWIN
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1893 Jun 21 (Box 13, Folder 987)
  - PARR, SAMUEL, 1747-1825
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1786-1811 (Box 13, Folder 988)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1822 Mar 18 (Box 13, Folder 989)
  - PARRY, EDWARD, BISHOP OF DOVER, 1830-1890
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1885, 1888 (Box 13, Folder 990)
  - PARSONS, JOHN, BISHOP OF PETERBOROUGH, 1761-1819
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1816, 1818 (Box 13, Folder 991)
  - PARSONS, WILLIAM, -1807
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1795 (Box 13, Folder 992)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806 (Box 13, Folder 993)
  - PASSLAY, [JOSEPH]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1799 Mar 29 (Box 13, Folder 994)
  - PAYNE, SARAH (BURNEY), 1796-
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1860] Jul 20 (Box 13, Folder 995)
  - PEARSON, GEORGE, 1751-1828
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1821 Feb 26 (Box 13, Folder 996)
  - PEEL, SIR ROBERT, 2D BART., 1788-1850
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1841 Sep 17 (Box 13, Folder 997)
  - PELTIER, JEAN-GABRIEL, 1770-1825
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1809, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 998)
  - PENNANT, THOMAS
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1773-74 (Box 13, Folder 999)
  - PENNECK, RICHARD
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1788 Jan 23 (Box 13, Folder 1000)
  - PENROSE, JOHN, 1778-1854
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1828] May 24 (Box 13, Folder 1001)
  - PEPYS, SIR WILLIAM WELLER, 1778-1845
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806-[ca. 1814] (Box 13, Folder 1002)
  - PERCEVAL, SPENCER, 1762-1812
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 Mar 2 (Box 13, Folder 1003)
  - PERCY, HUGH, BISHOP OF CARLISLE, 1784-1856
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1827 Aug 30 (Box 13, Folder 1004)
  - PERRY, JAMES, 1756-1821
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808-9 (Box 13, Folder 1005)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 Jan 18 (Box 13, Folder 1006)
  - PHILLIPPS, JOHN
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1806 Jul 14 (Box 13, Folder 1007)
  - PHILLIPS, MOLESWORTH, 1755-1832
    - Bond of Indemnity to Charles Burney, D.D., 1815 Mar 25 (Box 13, Folder 1008)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1831, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 1009)
  - PHILLIPS, SUSANNA ELIZABETH (BURNEY), 1755-1800
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1779]-94 (Box 14, Folder 1010)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1795-96 (Box 14, Folder 1011)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1796-98 (Box 14, Folder 1012)
    - Journal for her sister Fanny Burney D'Arblay: Folder I, 1786-87 (Box 14, Folder 1013)
    - Journal for her sister Fanny Burney d'Arblay: Folder II, 1787 Feb-Mar (Box 14, Folder 1014)
    - Journal for her sister Fanny Burney d'Arblay: Folder III, 1787 Apr-Jun (Box 14, Folder 1015)
    - Journal for her sister Fanny Burney d'Arblay: Folder IV, 1787 Jun (Box 14, Folder 1016)
    - Journal for her sister Fanny Burney d'Arblay: Folder V, 1787 Jul (Box 14, Folder 1017)
    - Journal for her sister Fanny Burney d'Arblay: Folder VI, 1787 Aug (Box 14, Folder 1018)
    - Journal for her sister Fanny Burney d'Arblay: Folder VII, 1787 Aug-Sep (Box 14, Folder 1019)
    - Journal for her sister Fanny Burney d'Arblay: Folder VIII, 1787 Oct (Box 14, Folder 1020)
    - Journal for her sister Fanny Burney d'Arblay: Folder IX, 1787 Nov-Dec (Box 14, Folder 1021)
    - Journal for her sister Fanny Burney d'Arblay: Folder X, 1787-1788 Jan (Box 14, Folder 1022)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1795 Mar 19 (Box 14, Folder 1023)
  - PHILLIPS, THOMAS, 1770-1845
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1815 Dec 4 (Box 14, Folder 1024)
  - PHILPOTT, HENRY, BISHOP OF WORCESTER, 1807-1892
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1847 (Box 14, Folder 1025)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1843 May 30 (Box 14, Folder 1026)
  - PIOZZI, HESTER LYNCH (SALUSBURY) THRALE, 1743-1821
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1777 (Box 14, Folder 1027)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1778 (Box 14, Folder 1028)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1779 Feb-Aug (Box 14, Folder 1029)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1779 n.d. (Box 14, Folder 1030)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1780-81 (Box 14, Folder 1031)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1782-1807 (Box 14, Folder 1032)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Jan 24 (Box 14, Folder 1033)
    - Letters to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1780, 1781 (Box 14, Folder 1034)
  - PISTRUCCI, FILIPPO, 1783-
    - Letter to Frances Burney, 1829 May 4 (Box 14, Folder 1035)
  - PITT, J.
    - Letter to [the first] Mrs. Charles Burney, [Ca. 1750] (Box 14, Folder 1036)
  - PLANTA, JOSEPH
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1812, 1815 (Box 14, Folder 1037)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 Apr 24 (Box 14, Folder 1038)
  - PLYMLEY, (CORBETT) JOSEPH, 1760-1830
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1803 Feb 9 (Box 14, Folder 1039)
  - PORSON, RICHARD, 1759-1808
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1786-96 (Box 14, Folder 1040)
  - PORTLAND, WILLIAM HENRY CAVENDISH BENTINCK
    [3rd Duke]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806 Jul 11 (Box 14, Folder 1041)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1809 Aug (Box 14, Folder 1042)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1809 Sep (Box 14, Folder 1043)
  - PRICE, SIR UVEDALE, BART., 1747-1829
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1808 Mar 9 (Box 14, Folder 1044)
  - PRIOR, SIR JAMES, 1790-1869
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1833 Jan 28 (Box 14, Folder 1045)
    - Letter to [Frances Burney d'Arblay], 1832 Jun 13 (Box 14, Folder 1046)
    - Letter to Frances Bentley (Young) Burney, 1862 Dec 2 (Box 14, Folder 1047)
  - PROUT, SAMUEL, 1783-1852
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1829-1840 (Box 14, Folder 1048)
  - R---, A. M.
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1781 Jan-Mar (Box 14, Folder 1049)
  - R---, T. L.
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 1050)
  - RAINE, JONATHAN, 1763-1831
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1811 Oct 8 (Box 14, Folder 1051)
  - RAINE, MATTHEW, 1760-1811
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1792-1808 (Box 14, Folder 1052)
  - RANDOLPH, JOHN, BISHOP OF LONDON, 1749-1813
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 May 29 (Box 14, Folder 1053)
  - RANDOLPH, M. L.
    - Letter to Rosette Burney, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 1054)
  - RAPER, FRANCES (PHILLIPS), 1782-1860
    - Letter to Rosette Burney, [ca. 1800] (Box 14, Folder 1055)
    - Letters to Mrs. Charles Burney, Jr., 1803, [1806] (Box 14, Folder 1056)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Jun (Box 14, Folder 1057)
  - REES, ABRAHAM, 1743-1825
    - Letter to [Charles] Burney, Mus.D., 1802 Feb 13 (Box 14, Folder 1058)